# Charlotte Asencio

### **CONTACT**

252-903-1274

charlotte.e.asencio@gmail.com

charlotteasencio.com

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelors of Social Work
Honors College
Belmont University, Nashville, TN

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

The Coding Bootcamp at UNC Charlotte

## **LANGUAGES**

Fluent in Spanish

## CONNECT



in www.linkedin.com/in/

#### **ABOUT ME**

As a developer with a background in Social Work, I am especially interested in the way technology can improve the world. I'm primarily a Front-End Developer with experience using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and various frameworks to build responsive web applications.

#### SIMILAR WORK EXPERIENCE

Study Programmer I
Clinical Ink

June 2018-Present Winston-Salem, NC

- Design and Build electronic source documents for clinical trials according to protocol specifications
- Program functionality and scoring into source documents utilizing JavaScript and C#

#### **PROJECTS**

**Proof of Concept** Clinical Ink

- Worked on the front-end for a proof of concept project for new internal software initiative that played a part in the approval of that initiative
- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Angular

#### Pay It Forward

Coding Bootcamp at UNC Charlotte

- An example web app that allows organizations to connect with volunteers including authentication and differing role permissions.
- Allows users with an organization account to post volunteer opportunities and users with volunteer profiles to sign up for those opportunities
- Technologies used: React, CSS, Firebase

#### **Helping Hands**

Coding Bootcamp at UNC Charlotte

- An early version of the Pay It Forward project that allowed anyone to post or sign up for opportunities with no differentiation between user roles and permissions
- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Node.js, Handlebars, MySql

# OTHER EXPERIENCE

Victim Services Coordinator
Forsyth County District Attorney's Office

April 2016-May 2018 Winston-Salem, NC

Support Team Coordinator
Safe Passage/ Camino Seguoro

Feb 2015-June 2015 Guatemala City, Guatemala